Let's see who dares kick me out
I'm carrying the Jiang family's blood
This is your grandson
Could you bear letting him wander the streets?
Stop pretending, you old hag
At your age
how could you possibly get pregnant?
This is a hospital
How could I lie to you?
Son, I'm begging you
I'm already ruined
The Jiang family's only heir
Come out here
I exposed my husband's affair with the maid
and got killed
This life
your family will pay in blood
Xiao Lan, come
come wash my feet
Zhang Guifen, don't push it
Oh my
My precious son says
he wants Grandma to serve him personally
If she doesn't serve him well
he won't come out
He'll just stay in there
Let's see who panics
You little cutie
Honey
Honey, calm down
Careful of the baby in her belly
If it weren't for the baby
carrying the Jiang family's blood
I'd have thrown you out long ago
Don't hurt the baby
Something's wrong
Jiang Chengang's look just now
that's no way to look at a daughter-in-law
Oh, Chengang
Gently now
I'm carrying your child
Don't crush it